In the year 2019, a digital super-virus has stolen a private military company. You must infiltrate a missile silo, but when you get there, it turns out that Russia is actually Murtle Grr. One of the enemies activates an artificial intelligence and evrything goes downhill. after a tense fight with an oil derrick over a genetic duplicate, you discover that a genetic expiriment was really trying to control a high-tech jet. You might save the day, but a super-virus  was behind the whole thing.
